Guide to the Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley records, 1970-2012.
Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley records,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley records, 1970-2012
7560
Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley.
65 cubic ft., 1 mapcase folder, 13 rolls of microfilm, 6.39 gigabytes
Records, publications, and periodicals.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Records of the organization and information on various services provided by GAGV. Also, information on the publication The Empty Closet and two sets of alphabetical subject files collected by the publication.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
On Oct. 3, 1970, around 100 people turned out for the first meeting of what was to become in 1973 the Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley – an event hosted by University of Rochester students Bob Osborn and Larry Fine with guest speakers from Cornell University, Ithaca’s chapter of the national Gay Liberation Front, and the Buffalo chapter of the national Mattachine Society, The new group called itself the Rochester Gay Liberation Front, the Rochester chapter of a group that started in N.Y.C., at Cornell and at University of Rochester after the Stonewall Riots in 1969. During the first year of the group’s existence, around 200 men and women, the majority of whom were non-students attended meetings and dances.
Because the majority of members were non-students, the Gay Liberation Front had left the University of Rochester campus in 1972. Later the Gay Alliance moved into a space in the Genesee Co-op, a renovated 19th century firehouse on Monroe Ave., where it stayed until a building at 179 Atlantic Ave. was purchased in 1990 to serve as the first Community Center.
In February 1973, a group of lesbians within the GAGV decided to split off and form their own group, GROW (Gay Radical Organization for Women), which became the Lesbian Resource Center (LRC), active until the ‘90s.
Gay lawyers and others helped to incorporate the GAGV by 1973, with the idea that the Alliance would be an umbrella organization for gay groups. The Speakers Bureau was founded by Karen Hagberg in 1970. The Bureau’s goal was to seek an accurate portrayal of gays in the media and to educate community groups about gay and lesbian people. Its efforts continue today.
The Empty Closet, which had begun its existence as a four-page ditto in January 1971, went to mimeograph in 1973, the first in a long series of format changes and technical upgrades, which continue to this day.
The mid ’80s was the time when the HIV/AIDS epidemic became the central gay male issue, and in Rochester as elsewhere, gay men (as well as lesbians and bi and transgender men and women) began the work of building grassroots organizations, like AIDS Rochester and Helping People with AIDS, to cope with the crisis locally and supply services for people living with HIV
The first Rochester Pride March took place on June 28, 1989. The Pride March, now the Pride Parade, continues today as a program of the Gay Alliance. By the late ’80s, the GAGV began to be seen as a service organization or human services agency, and the long process of transition began. Simultaneously, the Rochester queer community was growing and expanding its horizons. The Gay Alliance of the ‘80s began its emphasis on working with queer youth, who previously had no support whatsoever. The needs of the growing community meant that the GAGV had to become more of an institution than a grassroots activist organization.
The first big issue of the ’90s involving the GAGV was the fight for domestic partnership benefits for City of Rochester employees and their partners. The Alliance under the leadership of Lloyd Gray was part of a coalition of gay groups and individuals, and heterosexual allies, who led an intense campaign in 1994 to pass the legislation. City Council approved the measure after a heated debate. Also in 1994, the GAGV won its lawsuit against the City of Rochester, which had denied the non-profit group tax exemption. As a non-profit, the Gay Alliance primarily does social and cultural work and in the ‘90s it began to do its political work in a different way. The new mission statement made it clear that the agency is dedicated to empowering individuals and dealing with heterosexism and homophobia through education, support groups and advocating for an end to discrimination
Over the past decade the organization has shifted focus from grassroots political activism to the realities of creating a permanent community institution. In 2004, the Alliance moved from the tiny, outgrown Atlantic Ave. storefront to space at the Auditorium Center, 875 E. Main St. The Gay Alliance staff has grown over the years, enabling a dozen major programs to spring up which strive to meet the needs of everyone from teenagers to hate crime victims to families to elders. The Youth Group observes the Day of Silence each year and now takes youth on local college tours, as well as providing all kinds of supportive and empowering social activities and groups. Rainbow SAGE is in the process of becoming part of the Gay Alliance, in order to make its services to our elders as powerful and effective as possible. Trainings, InQueery events and Speakers Bureau presentations send our message throughout greater Rochester, to mainstream businesses, colleges, churches and service providers, as well as to LGBT individuals who need information, support and connection to their community.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Records of the organization and information on various services provided by GAGV, such as their community center, youth programs, and peer counseling hotline. Much of the collection is comprised of organizational records, such as board meeting minutes, financial and administrative records. Also included is information relating to events run by GAGV, such as the yearly Gay Picnic and the Sweetheart Ball. Files on community and political advocacy, grant proposals, and work with other New York State organizations are also included. Many of the files on other organizations include meeting minutes, notes, etc. Also, information on the publication The Empty Closet with two sets of alphabetical subject files collected by the publication and 13 rolls of microfilm with issues dating from January 1971 through February 2010. Includes correspondence, press releases, photographs, posters, and material about LGBTQ activism in Rochester and New York State from the mid-1970s through c. 2010. A letter from Robert Roth is included. Various feminist and gay publications and periodicals have been cataloged separately and listed at the bottom of the guide.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley.; Gay Revolution of Women.
Subjects:
Gay men--Societies and clubs--New York (State)--Rochester.; Lesbians--Societies and clubs--New York (State)--Rochester.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Boxes 34-35 and Boxes 63-65 are restricted until 2040.
Identifying information in Box 68, Folders 24-141 (Youth Program Folders) and box 69, Folders 9-11 is restricted for 75 years (until 2093). Demographic information and other descriptive characteristics may be used by researchers.
RELATED MATERIALS
Collecting Program: Human Sexuality Collection.
NOTES
Arrangement and description of the Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley records, #7560 made possible in part by a grant from the Documentary Heritage Program of the New York State Archives, a program of the State Education Department
SERIES LIST
Series I. Administrative Files
Boxes 1-2,12,34-35, 45-59
Boxes 34-35 are RESTRICTED
Directions Committee (DC)
General (1974-1988)
Correspondence
Board
Financial
Historical and General (1971-2007)
News clippings, Programs, and Other Published Materials
Chuck Bowen Files
Todd Plank Files
Series II. Events, Projects, and Services
Boxes 3-7, 12, 31, 34-45, 60-65, Mapcase Folder 1
Boxes 34-35; 63-65; Box 68, Folders 24-141 and Box 69, Folders 9-11 are RESTRICTED
1971-1984
Gay Community Services Project
The Empty Closet related
General
Political Work
Other Local Organizations
1993-2014
General Programming
Youth Related Programming
Parents and Families of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG) Files
Lilac Rainbow Alliance for the Deaf (LRAD) Files
Series III. Empty Closet
Boxes 7-27, 31
Alphabetical Subject Files 1971-1984
A-F
G-L
M-S
T-Z
Alphabetical Subject Files 1975-2004
A-F
G-L
M-S
T-Z
Alphabetical Photo File
Back Issues on Microfilm
Digital copies of Empty Closet
Series IV. Ephemera and Memorabilia
Boxes 28-33
Clothing
Pins and other Memorabilia
Certificates and Awards
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I: Administrative Files
  - Directions Committee
    - Discrimination in employment, Rochester- correspondence, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Elections- Gay Brotherhood of Rochester Ballots, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Empty Closet correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Social work field placement manual, correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Finance Committee correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Financial statements and budget, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - GayYellow pages- correspondence, 1973,1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - General information, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Legal Council- correspondence, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Library committee- correspondence, 1971, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Library Committee periodicals- correspondence, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - New Directions Committee by-laws list, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - NYS Coalition of Gay Organizations correspondence, Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - NYC Gay Activists Alliance correspondence, Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Office staff- Gay Brotherhood staff '74, rules, regulations and info., 1975 staff announcement, c. 1974, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Religious survey, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Rochester Community Church office use agreement, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Rochester Police Department correspondence re: transvestites, request for police speaker, 1971, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Rochester public library list of recommended books, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Speakers bureau, 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Stationary and letterheads; lists of medical people willing to treat transsexuals, Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence- miscellaneous incoming, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence- miscellaneous outgoing, 1972,1974 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Counseling- correspondence, calendar events, workshops, conference description, article reprint, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Counseling, military - Pvt. Robert Thayer, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Buffalo Gay Community Center- movie flyer and services brochure, Undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - By-laws, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - General (1971-1984)
    - GAGV Introduction letter, Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - GAGV tentative constitution, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Certificate of Incorporation, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Copies of Certificate of Incorporation, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Rochester Community Church office use agreement, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - First Unitarian Church- space rental, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Incorporation papers, constitution, by-laws, goals, 1975, 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Copies of various documents, 1973-1979 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - By-laws of GAGV, Undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Constitution and by-laws of GAGV (revision), 1980 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Proposed constitution and by-laws (revised), January 1980 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Constitution and by-laws (revised), February 1980 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - GAGV Policies, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Board member lists, rules, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Committee outlines, Undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Notes, Undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Media committee, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Media committee materials, c. 1979 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Application for Board Position forms, Undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Constituent network, Undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Board memos, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Board meeting minutes, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Board meeting minutes, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Board meeting minutes, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Annual Report, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 52-53)
    - Board meeting minutes, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Board list, March 1978 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Annual Report, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 56-57)
    - Plans: 3 and 5 year, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - President's Report, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Board meeting minutes, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Meeting reports, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Board elections, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Notes, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Board meetings, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - "Official Files" (Miscellaneous board materials), 1977-1980 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Personnel Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Personnel Policy Statement, Undated (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Employment Interview Verification form, Undated (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Job/Typing instructions forms, Undated (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Employment forms, Undated (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Office staff information, Undated (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Job descriptions, Undated (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Membership drive, Undated (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Miscellaneous administrative materials, 1977-1981 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Agenda 11/13 with margin notes on goals, Undated (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Finances, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Finances, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Financial reports- originals, 1975-1980 (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Financial statements, meeting minutes, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Finances, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Finances, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Finances, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Annual financial report, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - President's report/financial report, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Financial sheets, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Financial statements, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - Financial records, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - Bank notices, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - Financial reports, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - Financial statements, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - Budget information, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 92-93)
    - Treasurer's report, February 28, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 94)
    - Financial correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 95)
    - Lines of credit, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 96)
    - Chamber of Commerce, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 97)
    - General ledger, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 98)
    - Financial files, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Financial statements, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 99)
    - "Past Business" (financial materials), 1986 (Box 1, Folder 100)
    - Budget, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 101)
    - Donation forms, Undated (Box 1, Folder 102)
    - Donations, c. 1982 (Box 1, Folder 103)
    - Fund-raising, 1974, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 104)
    - Fund-raising, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 105)
    - Money request flyer, 1976? (Box 1, Folder 106)
    - "Money Needed" Ads, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 107)
    - New Housing fund-raising flyer, Undated (Box 1, Folder 108)
    - Unfinished proposals, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 109)
    - Grants, 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 110)
    - Grant proposals, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 111)
    - Grant researchers- Sumner, Hans + Associates, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 112)
    - Insurance, 1979,1981 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Workman's comp./disability/IRS tax papers, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Tax forms, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Three year comparison of income, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Tax, unemployment insurance forms/correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Tax statement, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Monthly payroll reports/information, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Alive magazine deadlines, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - David Gambino, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Development ideas, examples of newsletters, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Dick's application xerox, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - "Gay Community Center Records $7.00 Donation", Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Legal documents re: Richard Hopkins, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Legal bills, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Legal files, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Legal files, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - List of contributors, 1976? (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Membership brochure/flyers, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - GAGV Information pamphlets, Undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Membership Survey form, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Message/memo sheet, Undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Co-Presidents' file, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Co-Presidents' & amp; peer counseling files, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 2, Folder 24-25)
    - Miscellaneous, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Patricia Purcell papers, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Petty cash forms, Undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Petty cash sheets, thru 2/20/1980 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Photographs, Undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Press/news releases, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Press releases, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Press releases, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Printing, Undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Publicity, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Purchase order requisition form, Undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - GAGV stationary, Undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Temporary mail directory, Undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - University of Rochester student intern proposal, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Vince Di Schino records/check register, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - "What is Happening at 'Our' Alliance" by Rick Dixon, Undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Mailing lists- local community groups, Undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Mailing list, Undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Media mailing lists, Undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Political mailing list, Undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Miscellaneous mailing lists, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Membership/mailing lists, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Membership/mailing list, Undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - GAGV community needs assessment survey, Undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - "Welcome to the Gay Alliance of Genesee Valley Inc." info. poster, Undated (Mapcase-folder 1)
  - Correspondence
    - Miscellaneous cards, Undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - re: LaPensee resignation, Undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Canadian Gay Activists Alliance, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Miscellaneous, 1971-1974 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Socialism & amp; Human Liberation (prisoner correspondence), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Religious, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - City officials, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - United Cerebral Palsy Association, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Professional correspondence, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Invitations to the annual GAGV meeting, Jan. 1978 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Support letters from community agencies, clergy, doctors, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Support letters, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Support letter copies, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Miscellaneous, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 63-64)
    - Correspondence In, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Correspondence Out, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 67-68)
    - Information requests, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Fuori!, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Miscellaneous, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Information requests, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 72-73)
    - Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - re: Sen. Eckert's remarks, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - re: Rochester Museum & amp; Science Center harassment incident, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - re: Craft resignation, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Hastings (Police Chief), 1981 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - re: Collins resignation, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 80-81)
    - Gay Nurses Alliance- Thank You letter, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Project PLAN, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Editor's correspondence, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Advertising correspondence, Jan.-May. 1982 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Miscellaneous, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - re: increase in rent, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Correspondence with OMEGA, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Miscellaneous, 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 89-90)
    - Miscellaneous, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Correspondence, 1991-2003 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Board
    - 2006 Ballots, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Non-Harrassment Policy and Personnel Policy, 2004, Undated (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Budget Planning, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Board Meeting, September 2004 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Special Meeting -- May, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Board Meeting and Reports -- July, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Board Meeting and Reports -- August, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Board Meeting and Reports -- September, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Board Meeting and Reports -- October, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Board Meeting and Reports -- November, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Board Meeting Agendas and Strategic Plan, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - GAGV Strategic Plan 2002-2006, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Guidelines and Procedures, 2000, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Board Meeting Minutes, January-April 2003 (Box 35)
    - Contact Information Questionnaire, June 2003 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - 2003 Budget, June 2003 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - 2002 Annual Report, Flier and Card, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Trustee Report, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 14)
      Bankruptcy court notice
    - 1998 Annual Report, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - 2000 Annual Report, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - 1999 Annual Report, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - 2000 Annual Meeting, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - 2000 Annual Meeting -- Ballots, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Board Committee, Undated (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - 2002 Board Ballots, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Board Members, 2000-2003 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Board Orientation, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - 2000 Annual Report Pamphlet, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - Executive Committee, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - Board of Directors (1), 1998-1999 (Box 46, Folder 24)
    - Board of Directors (2), 1996-1999 (Box 46, Folder 25)
    - Board of Directors (3), 1994-1996 (Box 46, Folder 26)
    - Membership/EC Subscription Letters, Undated (Box 46, Folder 27)
    - Membership, Undated; FD-31 (Box 46, Folder 27)
    - Recruitment, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 28)
    - 2001 Board Ballots, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 29)
    - Rosters, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 30)
    - Board Retreat, 2000-2001 (Box 46, Folder 31)
    - 2001 Board Applications, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 32)
    - Community Center, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 33)
    - Osmosis Medialab, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 34)
    - Remit Envelope, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 35)
    - Board Roster, 2000-2001 (Box 46, Folder 36)
    - Board Meeting, June 2000 (Box 46, Folder 37)
    - Calendar & Financial Statements, 2000-2001 (Box 46, Folder 38)
    - Ideas for New GAGV Logo, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 39)
    - Policies, December 2000 (Box 46, Folder 40)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, March 2001 (Box 46, Folder 41)
    - 2001 Budget, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 42)
    - Board of Directors Minutes, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 43)
    - Board of Directors Minutes, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 44)
    - Board of Directors Minutes, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 45)
    - Board of Directors Minutes, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 46)
    - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 47)
    - Finance Committee Meeting, November 2001 (Box 46, Folder 48)
    - Finance Committee Meeting, June 2001 (Box 46, Folder 49)
    - Finance Committee Meeting, May 2001 (Box 46, Folder 50)
    - Finance Committee Meeting, April 2001 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    - Finance Committee Meeting, February 2001 (Box 46, Folder 52)